Guide to the King County Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Martin Luther King, Jr. County Labor Council records, 1965-2012; 1940-005; 6.56 cubic feet 7 boxes
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Records, 2000-2005; Series 1 (Box-folder 1/1-3/20)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Initiative 729, 2000 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Harborview Bond Initiative, 2000 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Seattle Parks Initiative/Prop. 1, 2000 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Healthcare, 2000 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Initiative 243, 2000 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Initiative 745, 2000 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Metro Transit/Prop. 1, 2000 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Gore, 2000 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - North Highline Fire District/Prop. 1, 2000 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Statewide Races, 2000 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislative, 2000 (Box-folder 2/6.1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislative, 2000 (Box-folder 2/6.2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, City of Seattle, 2001 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, King County, 2001 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Committee on Political Education 2001 - Mayoral Candidate Paul Schell (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Port of Seattle, 2001 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Committee on Political Education 2001 - Candidate Questionnaires, Seattle School Board (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Committee on Political Education 2001 - Schools First Levy, February (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Initiatives, 2001 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Legislative Action Committee, 2001 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Candidate Photos, 2001 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Mayoral Candidate Mark Sidran, 2001 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Federal, 2000 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Judicial Races, 2000 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislators, 2004 (Box-folder 2/20.1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislators, 2004 (Box-folder 2/20.2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Other, 2004 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Judicial, 2004 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, National, 2004 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Committee on Political Education 2004 - Initiatives & Ballot Measures (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Public Disclosure Commission Reports, 2004 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Other Cities (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, Seattle City Council (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, King County Council (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, Port of Seattle (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, King County Other (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, Seattle Other (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Candidate Questionnaires, Seattle School Board (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Initiatives & Ballot Measures (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Committee on Political Education 2005 - Public Disclosure Commission Reports (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Committee on Political Education - City Elected Vote Tracking, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Committee on Political Education - National Elected Vote Tracking, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Committee on Political Education - State Elected Vote Tracking, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Committee on Political Education - County Elected Vote Tracking, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1998-2012; Series 2 (Box-folder 3/21.1-4./1)
    - King County Labor Council meeting minutes 1998-2006 (Box-folder 3/21.1)
    - King County Labor Council meeting minutes 1998-2006 (Box-folder 3/21.2)
    - King County Labor Council meeting minutes 2007-2012 (Box-folder 3/22.1)
    - King County Labor Council meeting minutes 2007-2012 (Box-folder 3/22.2)
    - Misc. labor-related documents found in cupboard (Box-folder 4/1)
  - General Correspondence, 1993-2011; Series 3 (Box-folder 4/2-7/1)
    - ACORN, 1999-2008 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - ACLU sponsorship agreement, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - ANWR, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - AT&T Comcast, 2002 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Alliance for Sustainable Jobs & the Environment, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - ANEW, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Boeing, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Building Owners & Managers Assoc., 2003 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Brazilian Landless Worker Movement (Box-folder 4/10)
    - President George W. Bush, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Canadian Postal Workers, 2003 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Senator Maria Cantwell, 2002 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Carpenters Disaffiliation, 2001-2011 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Central Labor Councils, Washington, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Central Labor Councils, not Washington, 1994-2005 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - China PNTR, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Construction Workforce Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Economic Opportunity Task Force, 2002 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Elected Official Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Ergonomics, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Evergreen State College Labor Center, 1995-2009 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Experience Music Project organizing, 2000 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Fair Trade Coffee, 2002 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Globalization, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Globalization, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Globalization, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Globalization, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Globalization, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Hate Free Zone, 2002-2008 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Homecare; OPEIU/SEIU, 2001 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Immigration, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - General correspondeonce - Jobs With Justice, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Jones Act, 2000 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Ron Judd Roast invitation, 2000 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Just Health Care Coalition, 2000 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - King County Budget, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - General correspondence - King County Commission on Governance, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - King County Executive Ron Sims, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - General correspondonce - King County Growth Management, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - King County Labor Summit, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - King County Solid Waste Oversight Committee Gainsharing, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Labor in the Pulpits, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Labor/Religious Breakfasts, 1999-2006 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - LELO, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - MLK Day Celebration Committee, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Metro. King County Council, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Mine Workers, 2004 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Monorail Finance, 2003 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Monorail Operations & Maintenance, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/22.1)
    - Monorail Operations & Maintenance, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/22.2)
    - Monorail Misc., 2003-2006 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Monorail Misc., 2003 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Monorail Transparency Ad Hoc Committee, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Native American Coalition, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - PACCAR lockout, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Partnership for a Sustainable Washington, 2002 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Permanent Replacements, 2000 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Port Coalition Misc., 2002-2005 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Port Jobs, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Port of Seattle/Airport Project PLA, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Port of Seattle/Airport Concessions Bargaining, 2001 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Port of Seattle/Misc, 1995-2005 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Delegate Roll Call Sign-In Ledgers, 1965-1977; Series 4 (Box-folder 7/2-7/3)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll call sign-in ledger January 1965-December 1970, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll call sign-in ledger January 1971-December 1977, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 7/3)
- Martin Luther King, Jr. County Labor Council records, 1984-2011; 1940-006; 4 boxes and 2 banners 5.7 cubic feet
  Donated by King County Labor Council.
  Publications such as King County Labor News, delegate roll call ledgers, subject files on various topics, correspondence with affiliates, and banners from marches and events. This collection is primarily communications between the King County Labor Council and other labor organizations within the greater Seattle area. It is separated into five series: publications, delegate roll call ledgers, subject files, correspondence with affiliates, and banners from marches/events. The date range of the materials is from 1978 to 2011.
  The publications series is all issues of the quarterly organizational publication, King County Labor News, dating from 1987 to 1995.
  The delegate roll call ledgers series is three large ledger books containing signatures of KCLC delegates from 1978 to 1991, as well as several packets of spreadsheet sign-in ledgers.
  The subject files series contains contracts and bargaining agreements/negotiations from local unions, organizational resolutions, Seattle Union Now materials, and several KCLC campaigns, dating from 1985 to 2006.
  The correspondence with affiliates series is communications between the KCLC and local unions as well as labor rights campaigns and organizations and dates from 1982 to 2011.
  The banners from marches/events series is comprised of two canvas banners, the first from a KCLC Organizing for Change campaign and the second from the Fight for 15 campaign, c. 2014.
  - PUBLICATIONS: KING COUNTY LABOR NEWS, 1987-1995, SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1-1/9)
    - King County Labor News, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - King County Labor News, 1993 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - King County Labor News, 1994 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - King County Labor News, 1994 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - King County Labor News, 1994 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - King County Labor News, 1994 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - King County Labor News, 1995 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - King County Labor News, 1995 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - King County Labor News, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - DELEGATE ROLL CALL LEDGERS, 1978-1991, SERIES 2 (Box-folder 2/1-2/3, 1/10)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll Call Sign-in Ledger, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll Call Sign-in Ledger, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll Call Sign-in Ledger, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - KCLC Delegate Roll Call, 1992 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - SUBJECT FILES (Alphabetical), 1985-2006, SERIES 3 (Box-folder 1/11-1/22, 3/1-3/23)
    - Port of Seattle Terminal and Cruise Ship Work, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Port of Seattle Crane Maintenance (Part 1 of 4), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Port of Seattle Crane Maintenance (Part 2 of 4), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Port of Seattle Crane Maintenance (Part 3 of 4), 1994 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Port of Seattle Crane Maintenance (Part 4 of 4), 1985 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Renton Technical College, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - KCLC Resolutions (Part 1 of 3), 1999-2006 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - KCLC Resolutions (Part 2 of 3), 1999-2006 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - KCLC Resolutions (Part 3 of 3), 1999-2006 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Right to Organize/Seattle Union Now (Part 1 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Right to Organize/Seattle Union Now (Part 2 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Right to Organize/Seattle Union Now (Part 3 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Schwerin, Campbell, Barnard re GR-22, 2000 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - School of the Americas, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - SeaTac Airport Coalition (Part 1 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - SeaTac Airport Coalition (Part 2 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - SeaTac Airport Coalition (Part 3 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - SeaTac Airport Coalition, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - SeaTac Airport Jurisdiction, 2001 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - SeaTac Airport Third Runway, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Seattle Union Now [Exec. Committee Meeting, May 7, 1999] (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Seattle Union Now: Seattle Organizing Center (Prior to SUN), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Seattle Union Now: Union Cities (Part 1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Seattle Union Now: Union Cities (Part 2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Seattle Union Now: Seattle Organizing Committee (Part 1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Seattle Union Now: Seattle Organizing Committee (Part 2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Seattle Union Record (Part 1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Seattle Union Record (Part 2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Security Officers Union, 2002 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Steelworkers (Missing), 2001-2006 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Teamsters Apple Campaign, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - The Regional Partnership, 2003 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Transportation Reform and Improvement Plan (TRIP 21), 2000 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - U.S. Labor Against the War (USLAW), 2003-2006 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Unemployment Law Project, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 3/23)
  - CORRESPONDENCE WITH AFFILIATES (Alphabetical), 1982-2011, SERIES 4 (Box-folder 3/24-3/26, 4/1-4/15, 5/1-5/68)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute/Seattle Chapter, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Actors Equity, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Aerospace Machinists Dist. Lodge 751 (IAM), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Air Line Pilots Assoc., 2000-2011 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Air Transport Dist. 143 (IAM), 2000-2008 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Air Transport Local 1351 (IAM), 1997-2006 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - American Radio Assoc., 2001-2006 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Auto Machinists Local 289 (IAM), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Bellevue Police Managers Assoc., 1999-2001 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Boilermakers Local 104, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Boilermakers Local 502, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Bricklayers Local 1 WA, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Carpenters Local 131, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Affiliates - Carpenters Local 1797, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Carpenters Pacific NW Regional Council, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Carpenters Local 1144, 2001 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - KCLC Meeting and Delegates Meeting, 1991 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Cement Masons Local 528, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Classified Workers Local 4787 (AFT), 1995-2006 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Classified Workers Local 4795 (AFT), 1992-2006 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Clothing & Textile Workers Joint Board, 1982-2001 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Communications Workers Local 7800 (CWA), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Communications Workers Local 7803, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Communications Workers Local 14761, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Communications Workers Local 37082 (The Newspaper Guild) - Times/P-I Strike, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Communications Workers Local 37082 (The Newspaper Guild), 1997-2006 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Communications Workers Local 37083 (WashTech), 1998-2005 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - County & City Employees Council 2 (AFSCME), 2001-2006 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - County & City Employees Local 2170 (AFSCME), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - County & City Employees Local 21C (AFSCME), 1992-2003 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - County & City Employees Local 2084, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Deep Sea Fishermen's Union, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Electrical Workers Local 46 (IBEW), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Electrical Workers Local 77 (IBEW), 2000-2003 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Electronic Workers Local 1002 (IUEC), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Firefighters Local 27 (IAFF), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Firefighters Local 864 (IAFF), 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Firefighters Local 1461 (IAFF), 2003 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Firefighters Local 1604 (IAFF), 1985-2005 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Firefighters Local 1747 (IAFF), 2002-2003 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Firefighters Local 1760 (IAFF), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Firefighters Local 1810 (IAFF), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Firefighters Local 2919 (IAFF), 1991-2000 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Firefighters Local 3396 (IAFF), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Firemen & Oilers Local 193, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Flight Attendants Council 10 (AFA), 2003-2006 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - Flight Attendants Council 17 (AFA), 2002-2006 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Flight Attendants Council 19 (AFA), 2001-2003 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Flight Attendants Delta Campaign (AFA), 2001 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Glass Workers Local 50 (GMP), 2001-2006 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Glass Workers Local 68 (USW), 1996-2002 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Glaziers Local 188 (IUPAT), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Government Employees Local 1170 (AFGE), 2003-2005 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Government Employees Local 3197 (AFGE), 2000-2007 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - Government Employees Local 3937 (AFGE), 2004-2006 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Graphic Communications Local 767M (GCIU), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Graphic Communications District 2 (GCIU), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Inlandboatmen's Union of the Pacific/Puget Sound Region, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Inlandboatmen's Union of the Pacific/Region 37, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - Carpenters Local 1797, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 5/45)
    - Iron Workers Local 506, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 5/46)
    - King County Union Retirees Council, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 5/47)
    - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/48)
    - Laborers Local 1239 (LIUNA), 2000 (Box-folder 5/49)
    - Laborers Local 242 (LIUNA), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/50)
    - Laborers Local 252 (LIUNA), 1998-2002 (Box-folder 5/51)
    - Laborers Local 440 (LIUNA), 1991-2006 (Box-folder 5/52)
    - Letter Carriers Local 79 (NALC), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 5/53)
    - Locomotive Engineers Division 518 (BLET), 2001-2005 (Box-folder 5/54)
    - Longshore Bargaining 2002 (ILWU) (Box-folder 5/55)
    - Longshore Local 9 (ILWU), 2001-2006 (Box-folder 5/56)
    - Longshore Local 19 (ILWU), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/57)
    - Longshore Local 52, 1989-2006 (Box-folder 5/58)
    - Luggage Workers Local 51, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 5/59)
    - Lumber & Sawmill Workers, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5/60)
    - Machinists Local 79 & District 160 (IAM), 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/61)
    - Machinists Local 222 (IAM), 2000-2003 (Box-folder 5/62)
    - Marine Firemen, 1995-2005 (Box-folder 5/63)
    - Maritime Trades, Puget Sound Ports Council, 1995-2006 (Box-folder 5/64)
    - Masters, Mates & Pilots, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 5/65)
    - Metal Trades, Puget Sound Council, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/66)
    - Musical Artists (AGMA), 2002-2006 (Box-folder 5/67)
    - Musicians Local 76-493 (AFM), 1998-2005 (Box-folder 5/68)
  - BANNERS FROM MARCHES/EVENTS, SERIES 5
    - King County Labor Council AFL-CIO Organizing for Change, undated
    - 15 for Seattle, undated